<resources>
    <string name="app_name">bmiCalculator</string>
    <string name="calculate_your_bmi">Calculate Your BMI</string>
    <string name="severe_thinness_exercises">For severe thinness, focus on strength and muscle building exercises. Consult a fitness trainer for personalized workout routines.</string>
    <string name="moderate_thinness_exercises">Include resistance training and cardio exercises in your routine. Start with light weights and gradually increase intensity.</string>
    <string name="mild_thinness_exercises">Incorporate bodyweight exercises like push-ups, squats, and lunges. Also, include aerobic exercises to improve stamina.</string>
    <string name="normal_exercises">Maintain a balanced exercise routine with a mix of cardio and strength training exercises. Focus on staying active and healthy.</string>
    <string name="overweight_exercises">Emphasize cardio exercises like jogging, cycling, or swimming to burn calories. Include strength training to build muscle mass.</string>
    <string name="obese_class_i_exercises">Combine high-intensity interval training (HIIT) with strength exercises. Include activities like running, jumping jacks, and weightlifting.</string>
    <string name="obese_class_ii_exercises">Consult a fitness expert or a healthcare professional for personalized exercise programs. Focus on low-impact exercises to avoid strain on joints.</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email Address</string>
    <string name="password">Password (min 6 characters)</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="bmicalc">BMI Calculator</string>
    <string name="signup">Signup</string>
    <string name="enter_your_personal_information">Enter Your Personal Information</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="welcome_message1">Welcome to BMI Buddy, your personal fitness companion.</string>
    <string name="welcome_message2">Get ready to embark on a journey to a healthier you.</string>


</resources>